dollarade.com 2012-06-16

# Dollarade.com - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to Dollarade. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Dollarade collects, and the ways in which Dollarade uses that personal information.

**This privacy statement provides important information about the personal information that Dollarade collects, and the ways in which Dollarade uses said information.**

BY VISITING THIS WEBSITE AND REQUESTING INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEBSITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME AND CHANGES BECOME EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING. PLEASE CHECK BACK REGULARLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES. DOLLARADE WILL NOT NOTIFIY USERS OF CHANGES.

Notice to California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights: If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom Dollarade may have disclosed, within the past year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for that company's direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information, please email your request to contact@dollarade.com.

**Notice To/Regarding Children Under the Age of 13**

Dollarade believes that children using the Internet require special protection, and we urge parents or guardians to explain Internet safety to their children. Parents are urged to spend time online with their children to become familiar with the types of content available on the Dollarade sites and the Internet in general. Control tools are available from online services and software manufacturers to help create a safer environment for children.

If you are under 13 years of age, you should not provide any Personal Information (for example, your last name, home address or e-mail address) on these sites without the knowledge and permission of your parent or guardian. If Dollarade learns that you are under 13 years of age, Dollarade will not maintain or use any Personal Information about you without the verifiable consent of your parent or guardian, except as allowed by law. This may mean that you will be unable to participate in some activities on the sites without that verifiable consent. If a child under 13 years of age wishes to participate in any Dollarade website activity, or wishes to take advantage of a product or service offering available to children, and to do so necessitates the furnishing of any of the child's Personal Information, please note the following:

(i) The name, address, telephone number, and email address of the operator collecting or maintaining Personal Information from children through this website are as follows:

Dollarade P.O. Box 6701 Goodyear, AZ 85338 Telephone: 630-862-4508 e-mail address: contact@dollarade.com

(ii) The types of Personal Information collected from children may include the name, email address, home address, telephone number and/or any other information reasonably necessary for the child to participate in a particular activity. This information may be collected directly and/or passively (e.g., through a Web server that automatically recognizes and stores information such as a visitors IP address/domain name combination).

(iii) The information collected may be used for purposes such as fulfillment of a requested transaction, record keeping, marketing back to the child, or making it publicly available through a chat room or by other means.

(iv) Unless specific consent is obtained from the child's parent or guardian, the child's personal information will not be disclosed to third parties who are not contractors hired to carry out the internal operations of the websites, other than as may be required or permitted by law. We have required, or will require, such contractors to agree to use Personal Information of site visitors only for the purposes of carrying out these operations and to keep such information confidential. A parent or guardian has the option of consenting to the collection and use of the child's Personal Information without consenting to the disclosure of that information to third parties.

(v) Dollarade is prohibited from conditioning a child's participation in an activity on the child's disclosing more Personal Information than is reasonably necessary to participate in such activity; and

(vi) A parent can review and request deletion of the child's Personal Information, can refuse to permit further collection or use of the child's information, and can revoke or limit consents previously given. For instructions on how to do so, please send an email to:

contact@dollarade.com or write to us at:

Dollarade P.O. Box 6701 Goodyear, AZ 85338

Except as permitted by law, before any collection of a child's Personal Information takes place at a website directed to children or where Dollarade is knowingly collecting children's Personal Information, the child will be asked to provide his/her parents or guardians e-mail address so that Dollarade can contact the child's parent or guardian. Dollarade will then send an email (the "Initial Notification") to the parent/guardian indicating, among other things, the information that the child is requested to provide, the intended use(s) of the information and information on how the parent/guardian can, at their election, delete the child's information from Dollarade's database or records. Upon receipt of the Initial Notification, a parent or guardian may respond back to Dollarade to grant his/her consent or to deny consent in which case Dollarade will delete the parent/guardians email address and any other Personal Information, if any, previously obtained for securing parental consent. Upon Dollarade's receipt of the parent/guardian consent, Dollarade will send a confirming email to the parent/guardian email address or take such other action as may be required to verify the consent.

If Dollarade desires to use a child's information for purposes other than that for which the parent/guardian consent was previously given, Dollarade will not do so without first getting the parent/guardian consent.

**1\. Personal information collection**

Dollarade collects information from individuals by a variety of methods, including, but not limited to, when an individual voluntarily fills out a survey, order form, or a registration page either online or offline, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by Third Parties (collectively, a "Survey"). (As used herein, "online" means using the Internet, including the Websites, and related technologies, and "offline" means by methods other than online, including in person, in the postal mail, using telephones and cell phones, and other similar means.) In the Surveys, Dollarade or a Third Party may ask an individual to provide various information to Dollarade, which may include his or her name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time (together, "Survey Information"). Dollarade may also collect information concerning an individual from another source and use that information in combination with information provided from this web site. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and individuals are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to Dollarade or Third Party, but an individual may receive incentives from Dollarade or a Third Party in exchange for providing Survey Information to Dollarade.

**1.1 Site Membership or Registration**

To the extent registration is required to receive email and possibly postal communications from Dollarade or a Third Party Advertiser, this Privacy Policy also applies to consumers that have agreed to receive e-mail marketing from Dollarade or a Third Party Advertiser, whether at our Website, via email, on Third Party websites or otherwise. We collect information in certain portions of our Website, where guests provide content submissions and suggestions or participate in interactive online activities (i.e., by way of responding to questions and surveys, community listings, ratings, searches and comparison searches, bidding, purchasing, chat, games, or bulletin boards, etc.). The personal profile information you submit to Dollarade or Third Party Advertisers remains your property, but by submitting that information to Dollarade or Third Party Advertisers, you grant Dollarade and/or Third Party Advertisers, the right to use that information for marketing purposes. Dollarade or Third Party Advertisers may also use such information for content improvement and feedback purposes. We may sell the personal information that you supply to us and we may join together with other businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to you. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation. In addition, Dollarade reserves the right to release current or past information in the event Dollarade believes that the information is being or has been used in violation of the Rules or to commit unlawful acts, if the information is subpoenaed, if Dollarade is sold or acquired, or when Dollarade deems it necessary or appropriate. By agreeing to these terms, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any Third Party when Dollarade in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate.

"Subscription" occurs when an end-user registers for Dollarade's and/or Third Party Advertisers' services, either via registration at our website, via co-registration at a marketing partner's website, or via a permission pass / opt-out / no-opt mailing Dollarade collects personally identifiable information about our subscribers, based on: information gathered at the time of registration, subscriber interaction and response to subsequent electronic mailings and website use, information provided by marketing partners, and information appended from data aggregators. Information collected may include, but is not necessarily limited to: name, email address, postal address, gender, birth date, telephone number, activity, interests, user behavior and other demographic information. This information enables us to better tailor our content to subscribers' needs and to help our clients to promote and sell their products and services.

**1.2 Third Party List Information.**

Dollarade collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a Third Party and Dollarade subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the Third Party (the "Seller"). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual's name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, "Third Party List Information"). When acquiring Third Party List Information, Dollarade seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to Dollarade and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller's list.

Where Dollarade discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Dollarade may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**1.3 Other Information.**

Other occasions when Dollarade obtains information from individuals include (1) when an individual is making a claim for a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by Dollarade or by a Third Party, (2) when an individual requests assistance through Dollarade's customer service department, (3) when an individual voluntarily subscribes to a service or newsletter; (4) when private information is provided by means of a referral by a third party to Dollarade or a Third Party Advertiser (together, "Other Information").

**1.4 Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology.**

Dollarade currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about an individual with information about the individual in our database. Additionally, Dollarade may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future (together, "Technology Information").

(a) Cookies:

A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individual's computer that allows Dollarade to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in Dollarade's database. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. Individuals who use the Website need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Website.

(b) Web Beacons:

A web beacon is programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page (by using an  programming function -- see http://truste.org for more information), but can also be used to transfer an individual's unique user identification (often in the form of a cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows Dollarade to track certain web sites an individual visits online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services an individual may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes. For example, Dollarade might place, with the consent of a Third Party website, a web beacon on the Third Party's website where tennis products are sold. When bob, an individual listed in Dollarade's database, visits the fishing website, Dollarade receives notice by means of the web beacon that bob visited the tennis site, and Dollarade would then update Bob's profile with the information that Bob is interested in tennis. Dollarade may thereafter present offers of tennis related products and services to Bob. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, Dollarade also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in Dollarade's database.

(c) New Technology:

The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly evolving, as is Dollarade's use of new and evolving technology. As a result, Dollarade strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of technology.

(d) Usage Tracking:

Dollarade tracks information related to the electronic mailings and web pages viewed by users and subscribers, as well as the hyperlinks clicked by subscribers, while viewing our emails or visiting our websites.

(e) Log Files:

Log files are used to track and monitor subscriber usage.

(f) Optional Registration:

Dollarade may offer free voluntary registration to potential subscribers. During such registration, the subscriber is required to supply an email address and other personal information. This information is required if the subscriber wants to participate in Company services or Third Party Services.

(g) Feedback and Inquiries:

You have the ability to contact Dollarade to provide us with your feedback. Dollarade uses this information to respond to you and analyze customer service issues.

**1.5 Credit Card Information.**

Dollarade may in certain cases collect credit card numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card ("Credit Card Information") when an individual places an order from Dollarade. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to Dollarade, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. Dollarade will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the Credit Card Information will be disclosed to Third Parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction. Although Dollarade takes all commercially reasonable action to protect Credit Card Information, you ultimately assume the risk of any damage or loss as a result of transmitting such information to Dollarade, including but not limited to, identify theft, credit card fraud or credit card loss.

**1.6 Links to External Websites.**

Dollarade's emails and websites contain links to external websites. You will be taken to external websites if you click on these links. Your information may be passed from Dollarade's database to the external website, and/or external database, for your convenience (e.g. your information may be used to pre-fill a form at a destination website). Dollarade is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any external website owner. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any website they visit.

**2\. Use of Individual Information.**

**2.1 Discretion of Information.**

DOLLARADE MAY USE INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANY'S SOLE DISCRETION.

The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how Dollarade currently uses Individual Information, but Dollarade may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted below, Dollarade may update this policy from time to time. Dollarade may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

**2.2 Email and Unsubscribe Policy.**

Dollarade uses Individual Information to provide promotional offers by email to individuals. Dollarade may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To unsubscribe from all Dollarade's email lists, a person must send an email to Contact@dollarade.com. Dollarade 's unsubscribe process impacts only the future delivery of electronic mailings disseminated by Dollarade on its own behalf. You may still receive electronic mailings sent on behalf of Third Parties and your personal information may still be shared with Third Parties for use in offline marketing and data appends, including email appends.

You should also note that unsubscribing from Dollarade's electronic mailings will not automatically unsubscribe the subscriber's information from any Third Party associates and licensees of the data. Since Third Party associates and licensee partners maintain separate databases from Dollarade, and you will need to unsubscribe from each source individually, if desired. This allows you the freedom to pick and choose which subscriptions to maintain and which to discontinue.

**2.3 Content of Email Messages.**

In certain commercial email messages sent by Dollarade, an Advertiser's name will appear in the "From:" line but hitting the "Reply" button will cause a reply email to be sent to Dollarade. The "Subject:" line of Dollarade email messages will usually contain a line provided from the Advertiser to Dollarade.

**2.4 Solicited Email.**

Dollarade only sends email to individuals who have agreed on the Websites to receive email from Dollarade or to individuals who have agreed on Third Party websites to receive email from Third Parties. As such Dollarade does not send unsolicited email messages. As a result, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to Dollarade's email messages.

**2.5 Targeted Advertising.**

Dollarade uses Individual Information to target advertising to an individual. When an individual is using the Internet, Dollarade uses Technology Information (see also Section 2.7 below) to associate an individual with that person's Individual Information, and Dollarade attempts to show advertising for products and services in which the person has expressed an interest in the Surveys, indicated an interest by means of Technology Information, and otherwise. Dollarade may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.

**2.6 Direct Mail and Telemarketing.**

Dollarade uses Individual Information to advertise, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones and cell phones.

**2.7 Use of Technology Information.**

Dollarade uses Technology Information (1) to match a person's Survey Information and Third Party List Information to other categories of Individual Information to make and improve profiles of individuals, (2) to track a person's online browsing habits on the Internet, (3) to determine which areas of Dollarade's websites are most frequently visited. This information helps Dollarade to better understand the online habits of individuals so that Dollarade can target advertising and promotions to them.

**2.8 Profiles of Individuals.**

Dollarade uses Individual Information to make a profile of an individual. A profile can be created by combining Survey Information and Third Party List Information with other sources of Individual Information such as behavioral and other information obtained from public databases. Dollarade may also publish personal information in the form of a testimonial if such information is sent to Dollarade by you.

**2.9 Storage of Individual Information.**

Dollarade stores the Individual Information in a database on our computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Dollarade's control. Not withstanding such measures, Dollarade cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent our computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

**2.9.1 Securing your data**

Dollarade will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Dollarade will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

[Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.]

**2.9.2 Cross-border data transfers**

Information that Dollarade collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Dollarade operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

[In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the Internet and may be available around the world.]

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**3\. Dissemination of Individual Information.**

**3.1 Sale or Transfer to Third Parties.**

DOLLARADE MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN OOCEE'S SOLE DISCRETION.

**3.2 Order Fulfillment.**

Dollarade will transfer Individual Information to Third Parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a person orders from such Third Party while using Dollarade web sites or when responding to offers provided by Dollarade.

**3.3 Legal Process.**

Dollarade may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes.

**3.4 Summary Data.**

Dollarade may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

**3.5 Access.**

Individuals have access to their Individual Information collected to provide an opportunity for an individual to correct, amend, or delete such information. Access can be obtained by contacting contact@Dollarade.com. Dollarade may also grant advertising clients and email services providers' access to an individual's email address to verify the origin of the Individual Information collected.

**4\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties.**

**4.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons.**

Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, "Advertisers") who place advertisements on the Website and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Dollarade does not control Advertisers' use of such technology and Dollarade has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals.

**4.2 Links.**

The Website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the web sites of Third Parties. Dollarade is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Linked web sites may contain links to web sites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. Dollarade does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third Party web sites. The inclusion of a link to a web site does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

**4.3 Affiliated Companies.**

Dollarade may disclose, transfer, and sell Individual Information to entities affiliated with Dollarade in Dollarade's discretion. Should Dollarade be subject to an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of control or business entity status, Dollarade reserves the right to transfer or assign the Information collected from the Website.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Dollarade's treatment of your personal information, please email contact@dollarade.com.
